{
    "subject": "resource/Subhumans_(Canadian_band)",
    "predicate": "ontology/recordLabel",
    "object": "resource/Alternative_Tentacles",
    "human_readable": "Subhumans (Canadian band) was recorded by Alternative Tentacles.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9009416103363037,
            "question": "Is Subhumans a Canadian band?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8992456197738647,
            "question": "Who recorded the music by Subhumans (Canadian band)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8413469791412354,
            "question": "Who is known for recording with Alternative Tentacles?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7855241894721985,
            "question": "Is Subhumans (Canadian band) a popular band?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7758105993270874,
            "question": "Which record label released music by Subhumans (Canadian band)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6396982669830322,
            "question": "Name the record label that released music by Subhumans."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.638052225112915,
            "question": "What kind of music did Alternative Tentacles release?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5737797021865845,
            "question": "What genre of music is associated with Subhumans (Canadian band)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49252140522003174,
            "question": "What is the name of the Canadian band that recorded music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45583441853523254,
            "question": "Does Alternative Tentacles release punk music?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Subhumans (Canadian band) was recorded by Alternative Tentacles.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1698_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the Canadian band that recorded music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1698_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre of music is associated with Subhumans (Canadian band)?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1698_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of music did Alternative Tentacles release?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1698_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1698_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1698_117.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1698_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1698_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1698_134.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1698_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1698_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1698_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1698_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1698_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples you'd like me to evaluate!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I found that:\n\n* The Canadian punk rock band \"Subhumans\" is mentioned in several documents, and their albums were released by Alternative Tentacles. Specifically:\n\t+ In file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1698/re-ranker-msmarco/26.txt, it says: \"The Subhumans on this record... had their records released by Alternative Tentacles...\"\n\t+ In file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1698/re-ranker-msmarco/118.txt, it mentions a re-recording of an album called \"Same Thoughts Different Day\" which was originally released by Alternative Tentacles.\n* Therefore, the information in the documents supports the statement that Subhumans (Canadian band) were recorded by Alternative Tentacles.\n\nSo, the final answer is:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that the album \"Death Was Too Kind\" is released by Alternative Tentacles, and also describe it as containing the first three singles from Subhumans, a Canadian punk rock band. This supports the statement that Subhumans was recorded by Alternative Tentacles."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}